Okay, this factory is breeding
mosquitoes. A hundred million of them
every week. What? Why? Mosquitoes spread
lots of dangerous diseases to humans,
many of which we don't have vaccines or
treatments for. But, these are not
ordinary mosquitoes. They've been
infected with a bacteria that prevents
them from spreading certain diseases
like dengue. And when they're released
into the wild, they breed and then pass
on that bacteria to other mosquitoes.
And this all sounds scary, but it's
working. They released the mosquitoes
into a city in Brazil and they reduced
the amount of dengue by 69%.
And again in Indonesia, where dengue
dropped by 77%. And now, Google wants to
release 32 million mosquitoes into
California and Florida. To see what
happens here, subscribe.